travelreveal.com 2012-06-13

# Privacy Policy of Travelreveal.com – deny unauthorized access to application.

Company respects your privacy and recognizes the need to protect personally identifiable information collected by **www.travelreveal.com,** when you access the website we would like to guarantee you that we follow appropriate ethics and regulates the following policy.

We will collect information like your name, e-mail id, date of birth, gender, holiday preferences etc., only when you choose to register at our website for certain services provided by travelreveal.com

**Travelreveal.com** uses this information to fulfill your request for certain information, product and services and to update you about the latest of travelreveal.com

When you visit our website we collect the information like your IP address, program used, the time spent, portion of the website accessed which may be stored in our server as you access our site i.e. travelreveal.com but such information is not personally identifiable information. This information is used for the improvement of the website to analyze the number of visitors to the various portion of our site, to identify system performance or problem areas, so that we can improve our service to you.

We will not sell, trade, rent or disclose any information which is personally identifiable, with third party without your consent. Unless it is required for any legal process or in the case of great harm to the users or others.

We will take all the relevant steps to protect the personal information you share with us. We have proper technology and security features as well as strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access and improper use or disclosure. We will make it a point to enhance our security procedure and new technology time to time.

We see to it that your personal information is not shared by any of the advertisers on our website nor are they able to fetch any of your personal data.

Though **travelreveal.com** allows all ages of users, we recommend against children under the age of 13 submitting any information to our website. Also, we recommend you to take your parent/ guardian’s permission before providing any personal information to us if you are aged 16 or under. **Travelreveal.com** reserves the right to change or amend this policy. If we make any changes that can affect your personal information that we have already collected from you then we will make necessary efforts to notify you about the changes and to give you the options to amend or cancel your registration.

We recommend you to go through the privacy policy each time you intend to provide personal information.
